(Sheldon(Squirting him with a water spray):)Bad Leonard.
(Bethany:)So, what do you guys do?
(Howard:)Oh, you know, goth stuff.
Goth magazines, goth music.
(Raj:)Goth food.
(Sarah:)What's goth food?
Uh.... Blackened salmon?
(Bethany:)No, I meant, what do you do for jobs?
(Raj:)-Oh, we're scientists.
-Yeah, you know, the dark sciences.
What are the dark sciences?
(Raj:)Well, I am an astrophysicist,
and a lot of that takes place at night.
(Raj:)When there are vampires
and miscellaneous undead out and about.
[MUTTERS IN YIDDISH]
(Raj:)That sounds really cool.
(Howard:)Does it?
Well, okay, if you like space stuff...
...I designed components
for the space station. Which is in space.